roadfood.com 2019-04-06

# privacy policy | Roadfood

_Last updated: October 24, 2018._

Teneology, Inc. DBA Fexy Media (“Fexy,” “we,” “our,” and/or “us”) operates a platform that helps people discover and enjoy new recipes and meals. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) explains how we collect, use, and share your personal information. We own and operate several websites and apps (individually “Fexy Site” or “Fexy App,” collectively “Fexy Sites and Apps”). This Privacy Policy applies to those websites, apps, and any Fexy Sites and Apps that we operate, including Roadfood.com, or any online service where this Privacy Policy is posted (our “Services”).

**Personal Information We Collect**

**A. Information You Provide To Us**

**Registration Information.** You may be able to register for a Fexy account and/or another account on the Services. If you register for an account, we will receive any registration information you provide to us, for example, your name, username that you select, zip code, and email address. Note that we may migrate your account information to a single Fexy account as we develop our Services. If you decide to sign up for an account using a third-party account such as your Google account or your Facebook account, we will also get basic information from the profile associated with your account, such as your name and the email address associated with the account.

**Content Contributions.** You may be able to contribute to the Services in a variety of ways, for example filling out your profile, writing comments, etc. We may store these contributions and the dates and times you make them, and use them in different ways, including for display on the website.

**Communications**. If you contact us directly, participate in any of our surveys, or otherwise complete any online forms on the Services, we may receive additional information about you. For example, when you contact our customer support team, we may receive your name, email address, the contents of a message or attachments that you may send to us, and other information you choose to provide.

**B. Information We Collect When You Use the Services**

**Device and Usage Information.** To help us understand how you use the Services and to help us improve them, we automatically receive and log information from your device and information about your interactions with the Services, including IP address, MAC addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, the pages or other content you view, your actions on the websites and online services, and the dates and times of your visits. We also use your IP address to approximate your location and suggest grocery partners that may serve your area.

**Information from Cookies and Similar Technologies.** We collect information through the use of “cookies,” tracking pixels, and similar technologies to understand how you navigate through Services, to learn what content is popular, and to help us improve our algorithms and the offerings on the Services. Cookies are small text files that web servers place on your device; they are designed to store basic information and to help websites and apps recognize your browser. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be accessed every time you use the Services. We also use analytics providers such as Google Analytics cookies for these purposes, and you can find more information on how Google uses data from these cookies at [google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). These analytics providers may collect or have access to information about you which they may collect over time and across different websites. You should consult your web browser(s) to modify your cookie settings. Please note that if you delete or choose not to accept cookies from us, you may be missing out on certain features of the Services.

**C. Other Information We Collect from Third Parties**

**Fexy Sites and Apps.** If you sign up for an account or otherwise use the Fexy Sites and Apps, or you log into one of our websites or apps using an account affiliated with one of the Fexy Sites and Apps, such as your Serious Eats account or Simply Recipes account, we may receive and combine information about you, such as your recipes, zip code information, and shopping carts. We use this information to provide the shopping cart service, as well as personalize your experience, and make relevant recommendations to you on the Services, and learn about trends and patterns that we can share with our third party partners on a de-identified aggregate basis.

**Sites and Apps with Fexy Integration.** We receive information about your recipes and shopping carts from all Fexy Sites and Apps as well as other third party sites and apps that integrate our shopping cart technology. This allows us to provide you with an easy dashboard for viewing your recipes and ordering your ingredients and supplies.

**Grocery Partners.** Our Services are integrated with various grocery store partners so that you can easily purchase ingredients and supplies for your next great meal. If you choose to use our grocery partners’ integrated services, you will be directed to our partners’ websites to complete your purchases. When you purchase from one of our partners through our Services, the partner may provide us aggregate data or other summaries of the items our users purchased. We will use this information to learn about trends and patterns that we can share with our third party partners on a de-identified aggregate basis.

**How We Use The Information We Collect**

We use the information we collect from users to:

  * Provide you with the Services to allow you to discover and create the best recipes from around the country;
  * Improve, expand, and promote the Services;
  * Analyze how users interact with the Services in order to enhance user experience;
  * Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our Fexy Sites and Apps, including for tailored marketing and promotional purposes, and to distribute surveys;
  * Customize our offerings for you;
  * Provide you with customer support;
  * Learn about trends and patterns related to recipes and ingredients on a de-identified aggregate basis; and
  * Address legal issues that may arise, comply with our legal obligations and potential requests from authorities.

**How We Share The Information We Collect**

**Fexy Sites and Apps.** We may share information we collect about you between and among the Fexy Sites and Apps. All information collected through any Fexy Site or Fexy App will be shared with Fexy Media.

**Sharing on the Services and on Social Platforms.** You may be able to post comments and contribute other content on the Services. This information will be displayed publicly and will be visible to all other users and visitors to the Services. You can also choose to share recipes and other content you view on the Services through social media channels such as Facebook and Twitter and via email.

**Grocery Partners.** We will use your information to approximate which of our grocery partners serve your area and connect you with those grocery partners. We will share certain information, such as your ingredients and supplies with grocery store partners in order to facilitate your checkout. Note that you may provide our grocery partners with information when you purchase items or otherwise interact with their websites or apps. Please note that the information you provide directly to our grocery partners is not governed by this Privacy Policy, and you should consult their privacy policies to learn more about how they handle your information.

**Sites and Apps with Fexy Integration.** When you shop recipes through Fexy Sites and Apps or other sites and apps that integrate our shopping cart technology, we may provide those other sites and apps with de-identified, aggregated trends and patterns, such as how many times a certain ingredient was ordered. ** **

**Third Party Partners.** If you purchase ingredients and supplies via the Services, we will de-identify information about what you purchased and where you purchased it from and combine it with similar information from our other users. We will then share that information with our third party partners so that they can learn about trends and patterns related to what our users purchase. ** **

**Service Providers.** We work with third party service providers to perform services on our behalf, and we may share your information with such service providers to help us provide the Services, including to do all of the things described in Section titled “How We Use the Information We Collect.”

**Third Party Advertisers.** When you visit our Services, third party advertisers may set and access their own cookies, pixel tags, and similar technologies on the Services and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you that they collect over time and across different websites. We and third party advertisers may target advertisements for products and services in which you might be interested based on your use of the Service. If you prefer to not receive targeted advertising, you can opt-out of some network advertising programs that use your information. To learn more about your choices, please visit the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) Opt-Out Page: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>, or the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) Opt-Out Page: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

**Other Sharing.** We may share your Personal Information with other third parties in the following cases:

  * While negotiating or in relation to a change of corporate control such as a restructuring, merger or sale of our assets;
  * If a government authority requests information and we think disclosure is required or appropriate in order to comply with laws, regulations, or a legal process;
  * With law enforcement officials, government authorities, or third parties if we think doing so is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of Fexy Media, the Services, or our users;
  * To comply with a legal requirement or process; and
  * Whenever you consent to the sharing or as otherwise permitted or required under applicable law.

**Your Choices**

**Email Subscriptions.** You can always unsubscribe from our promotional emails but we will still send you transactional emails related to the Services.

**Editing and Accessing Your Information**. You can review and edit certain account information and request to close your account, by contacting us at [info@roadfood.com](mailto:info@roadfood.com) with your request. Please note that in some cases we may retain certain information about you as required by law, or for legitimate business purposes to the extent permitted by law. We may also retain your de-identified and aggregated data.

** ** **Do Not Track.** At this time we do not respond to Do Not Track signals.

**Other**

**Data Security.** We are committed to protecting your information. Even though we take reasonable precautions to protect your data, no security measures can be 100% secure, and we cannot guarantee the security of your data.

**Children’s Privacy.** The Services are not directed to children, and we don’t knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If we find out that a child under 13 has given us Personal Information, we will take steps to delete that information. If you believe that a child under the age of 13 has given us personal information, please contact us at:

Roadfood, Inc.  
7525 SE 24th Street, Suite 650  
Mercer Island, WA 98040

**Note to International Visitors.** The Service are hosted in the United States and intended for visitors located within the United States. Please do not use the Services if you are located outside of the United States. If you do use the Services from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personal information outside of those regions to the United States for storage and processing. By providing any information, including personal information, on or to the Services, you consent to such transfer, storage, and processing.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy.** We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, we will let you know through the Services, by email, or other communication. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy periodically to stay up-to-date about our privacy practices. As long as you use the Services, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy and any updates we make to it.

**Contact Information.** Teneology, Inc. DBA Fexy Media is responsible for your information described in this Privacy Policy. Feel free to contact us at any time with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your information, our use and sharing practices, or your choices by contacting us at info@roadfood.com.
